Oho, Big Mac's most favorite lemon poppy
seed muffins in town. After I hand him
these, maybe he will ask me to marry him
right then and there.
Waiting for my love.
tried everything.
>> Big Max Muffins.
Uh hello there.
>> Everything coming right back.
I need you to stay right there.
I'm coming right away.
Clean sweep. Don't move.
tried everything coming right Right.
>> Hello,
>> Saurin. There's something important we
need to talk about. About Brayburn.
>> You've got him on the ropes. Apple
bottom. Keep going.
>> What about him? He and I are in
Manhattan right now at the club.
Brayburn and Apple Bottom are doing a
dance battle where the winner gets four
free cans of Dr. Pepper.
>> Who are you then?
>> Big Mac. Big Mac's here too with future
Saurin.
>> Phew. I thought he was home.
>> We all wanted to get away as a sort of
vacation.
>> I'm glad he's safe and with the rest of
you, but I'm confused.
>> Clean sweep. What's happening in
Ponyville? Well, there doesn't seem to
be a Ponyville left.
>> Guess what? Bad [__] just won four Dr.
Peppers.
>> You brought parcel core to a gay strip
club. He's a baby. Are you stupid?
>> My pops wanted a drink to go with his
bountiful amount of cigarettes.
>> You're stupid, too. If you're defending
it, [__]
>> Pooky, that's enough. It's none of our
business.
Why isn't it eating?
>> I'm telling you, because it's an
oblivion pony, it probably wants blood,
not applesauce.
>> I don't care what it wants. The apple
family rules say that baby apples are
strictly prohibited from eating
non-Apple foods for the first year of
their life to indoctrinate them on
family values.
>> But it's not part of the apple family.
It's technically not even real. It's a
drawing you did out of crayons.
>> Then prove me wrong, [__]
Now that he's done crying and vomiting,
I'm going to go put him upside down in
our car with black tinted windows where
it's 98° outside and we can check up on
him in 6 or 7 hours.
You fools. You absolute dumb. Because
you fed me pony blood, I have been
rejuvenated back to my glorious form.
Interesting. Very interesting. The head
of this body you've been hosting has
been regrowing underneath your own for
the past year. Since your transplanted
head is saturated with my magic, the
body now accepts both as valid. Meaning
you can switch between your own head and
the body's original one whenever you
want.
>> So which one is the real one? Which one
is mine?
>> Your nervous system no longer
distinguishes one as more real than the
other. So when one is destroyed, the
body immediately resolves into the
alternate template to maintain
continuity. You essentially possess two
interchangeable heads occupying the same
existence. And frankly, I have no idea
what long-term consequences that will.
Welcome one and all to the Kieran's
Wish, a special kind of Kieran event in
which those who choose to participate
may do so only once in their lives,
where whoever wins can wish for
anything. their greatest desire to come
true.
>> Anything.
>> If that sounds enticing to you, all you
have to do is press the button in front
of you to confirm you want to play. The
only rule up front is that every single
one of you must press that button or
nobody gets to play.
>> Are you going to tell us anything else
like how the games even work?
It would appear to Brayburn and Saurin
and Big Mac and I that it does not seem
wise to move ahead before we know more
about this situation.
I'm afraid it seems none of you will be
participating in the Kieran's wish at
this moment. But no matter my Kirins,
this kind of thing happens. Mr.
Friendship, Mr. for Brayburn, Saurin,
and Big Mac. You four have 24 hours to
deliberate, and you will be brought back
here tomorrow. Should you decide that
you would like your greatest wish to
come true, the games will begin right
away.
>> Are we thinking that the Kieran's wish
can change anything, like even mental
things?
>> The mysterious mas
will.
>> There's my sexy man. Haha. Thanks,
Saurin. Brayburn, how long do the pot
pies go in the oven again?
>> How long in the oven though?
>> Lol. Wouldn't you like to know? I'm gay.
>> OMG, I have that same shirt kind of.
>> So, do you think I could just wish away
my schizophrenia?
>> Well, that's a terrible wish.
>> More like a perfectly perfect wish. I
talk to ponies in my head that aren't
even real.
>> Yes, you do. And that's the part of you
I love the most. Now I have to organize
my mail all over again.
>> You like me like this. It turns you on
how crazy and distracting I am.
>> Well, I didn't say that. Pop.
>> I'm easy to manage right now, aren't I?
That's why you'd hate for me to become a
little bit more sane. Oh, there's my
little postal pony [__] You want to
drag me into the other room and throw me
on the dirty bathroom floor and wreck
me, don't you? You have an active
imagination.
>> I probably am imagining things. Seeing
things that aren't there is my curse. So
help me win the Kieran's wish so I can
wish for a better brain.
>> It would be fun if you were more sane
and could take control of me from time
to time.
>> Oh, you are so into me.
>> Wow, what's that smell?
>> We're making pickled jalapenos. Brayburn
was getting homesick. Since we've been
away from Appaloosa for so long, we
decided to bring some of the cow pony
vibes here with us. I call pickled
jalapenños cowboy candy because it's
sweet like candy.
Me and the Brurn from my timeline used
to make cowboy candy together, too. It
was my favorite.
>> We've been boyfriends for almost a year,
and you've never asked me to make you
cowboy candy. Well, that's because it's
a Saurin and Braburn activity, just like
how a Saurin and Big Mac activity is
making lemon poppy seed muffins.
>> Where did you get those?
>> We made them before the trip.
>> Huh? I guess it does make sense for
boyfriends to bake together. I'll have
you know I bought you some this morning.
>> You didn't give me any
>> cuz the bag got blown up. Kublam,
>> tell me more about this Kieran's Wish
event you all were called to participate
in.
>> No pony knows anything. what happens in
the event or why any of us were even
selected.
>> You zata can only be funino and sina's
greatest wish is granted. What would you
want to wish for?
>> If you had asked me that a year ago, I
would have so many things, but I don't
know. I already have everything I want
with you being in my life. But the
masked Kieran said that if even one pony
backs out, nobody gets to participate.
I'm sure there's at least one pony who
does have a wish that deserves to come
true.
>> What do you want to wish for kitten?
You've got to have something since you
were the first to press the button.
>> What I want to wish for.
I was going to bed.
Lil Petey, I don't give a [__] that
you're a weird clone abomination of me
who came out of a cloning machine I
bought on the Tik Tok shop. Just like I
don't give a [__] about how Dog Man is
literally a dog's head on a human body
whom of which I have sex with. You're my
son. You are our son and we are a family
up in this [__]
My father, he was hardly away for a long
time. No matter what he did to me,
I went to the place every pony goes to
when they need a place to hide.
Ma'am, I don't actually work here. I'm
just the janitor.
>> Doesn't matter. I still got a coupon.
>> That coupon's out of date. It was for
yesterday.
>> I am God. The concept of time does not
apply to me.
>> I don't think that's how it works.
>> I want to speak to your manager.
>> Sorry.
>> Care package. I have been
inconvenienced. Attack.
>> Trust me. Re knows it is easy to make
friends in a mall. I read that on the
horse internet. All right. And we must
take every opportunity to make friends
if we want friends. All right. Beginning
in the mall food court. All right. Buy
me some orange chicken. Hello. Hello.
Hello. They're not coming. Perhaps this
is not a good place to make friends. I
am experiencing the emotion most would
call sadness right now. I'm going to go
in back to take some orange chicken
while nobody is looking. You be my
lookout.
Cheese and crackers. If ponies will not
be our friends willingly, then perhaps
we can rebuild already deceased ones and
have them teach us friendship by force.
Are you saying you want to bring this
one back to life as another puppet like
me? It would be more like a zombie or
ghoul. The detached head is cold, but
the heart still faintly beats and could
possibly be brought back to life with
another sprain. Okay, well, whose brain?
There is an infinite amount of parallel
timelines and worlds. If we can just
take the head of this individual from
the Equestria Girls universe and put it
on this one's body, that should work.
Why the Equestria Girls universe
specifically? Hasbro does not care about
male My Little Pony characters enough to
put effort into designing them. Which is
why Big Mac is white. If we take a male
character from this universe, nobody
will even notice they are missing.
That Big Mac is pretty handsome for a
human. This pony named Clean Sweep is so
irrelevant in the grand scheme of things
that it was a stock image of a cat in
the background of one scene in the
Equestria Girls universe. After being
brought to the world of ponies, I not
only had my own memories, which were
mostly just memories of myself eating
cat food and of myself waiting to eat
cat food, but also the body from the
years of abuse it suffered. I can't
really say for sure if I'm more cat or
pony or a perfect combination of the
two. I think my wish is to go back home.
I don't know if I have much of a place
in this one since if they're being
honest, not that many ponies like me.
And the clean sweep those body I took
could maybe even have another shot at
life.
That was dramatic of you telling us your
life story and ending it with you
telling us you want to leave.
>> I didn't plan on it being dramatic. Felt
right to finally say it, I guess. Do you
think I'm making the right choice to
want to go home?
>> I sure do.
>> That fast. I want you gone. So, yes.
Sounds like a chance of a lifetime for
me.
>> You're brutally honest.
>> I've lived for so long that I can't
stand when ponies beat around the bush.
Nothing unsettles me more than wasted
time. It's why I can say it to your
feline face that you're my greatest
obstacle at being happy.
>> An obstacle.
>> You're too close to Big Mac for my
comfort. He's my boyfriend, not yours.
>> I'm not going to deny you on that. I
love Big Mac. Not because I lost someone
else and needed somewhere for all that
feeling to go, like some pony. But I
have for him is real love. Watch it.
Brayburn.
You still love your braver and part of
you always will.
You can't give him your all. And Big Mac
is your second chance. You care about
him. I'm not saying you don't, but it
can't be the same level as what I feel
for him. You've got powers to make
things that inconvenience you disappear.
Why haven't you done it yet?
>> I thought about it. Don't think I
haven't. So then go all Vict Alicorn
Prince on me right now.
>> If I did, he would hate me.
>> Yeah, he because Big Mac loves me too.
>> But I'm sure Big Mac would forgive me
after enough time.
>> Would he?
>> I could erase you before you even step
into that stupid Kieran's wish event,
[__]
>> Yes. Yes, you could.
Don't push me far enough that I stop
caring about what Big Mac thinks. You'd
better win and get your wish, Puny
Kitten. What? You heard me. Because if
you don't, I won't hold back any longer.
What's with you? Why can't you just not
hold back now? Just end me here and now
so that I don't have to Valk out of Big
Mac's life on my own.
Why didn't you say yes to participating
in the Kirin's wish? Why don't you tell
me why you said yes first? Cuz I'm
broken. Broken. Broken. Broken. You are
not broken. You are just sick with
something. Okay. Sick. But if I win, we
can wish for me to be cured of my
mystery ill illness. We could take it a
step further. Friendship. We can wish to
be real life ponies like the others. I
won't be an ugly clown clown puppet. And
you won't be an ugly blanket. I admit I
am not the most pleasant to look at, but
I do not think I am ugly. You're the one
who cries about how you'll never have
friends. If you want friends, we've got
to look just like the rest of them. I do
not like the idea of changing as a means
to please others. So, you won't
participate in the Kieran's wish and
turn me into a pony, even if I beg you
for it. The Arin knows you are now is
the one I love. You're my best friend.
I'm your only friendship and you're
mine, too. But you're not being a good
one to me right now.
Are you mad at me?
>> Why wouldn't he be?
>> Why are you here, Parcel Core?
>> My brother here is a dreamer and he's
forced to be paired up with something
like you who's got no wish for yourself.
>> I already made one wish in my life and
it satisfied me to the fullest. And that
was Arino's creation. I don't need any
more wishes. And if I'm not satisfied,
friendship.
>> Exactly. And if he's not satisfied,
I don't want to steal Arinos away from
you, but I don't think he likes parading
himself as a clown for your amusement.
He's the one who dresses himself like a
clown. It is his fetish which I simply
indulge in with him for his sake.
>> Do you know why my brother Arenos ising
glitching?
>> He and I are both currently studying to
figure out the cause. I asked you a yes
or no question.
>> No, I do not know the cause.
>> Well, if you haven't [__] figured out
the cause, why not let him make his most
desired wish and be cured?
>> What Arinos wants is too ambitious. I do
want him cured, but not for him to
become a flesh and blood pony
>> because he would no longer be your
little puppet [__]
Have you had enough time to deliberate?
I hope so, for I ask again. What is the
wish you desire most? This is your one
and only chance to obtain it, so don't
waste it.
And with that, the Kieran's wish may
begin.
Bring out the sacred door of wishes.
One at a time, my ugly pony friends.
Don't rush things, but don't take too
long. After all, this is for the
enjoyment of the Kirin race. Mom, Dad,
I'm so happy you're here. This will be
my first real family trip with you as a
fullgrown stallion.
>> Extended family trip.
>> So, is the Kieran's wish thing we're
supposed to be looking for somewhere
around here? Should we start climbing
the stairs to look for it, or should we
separate in groups or stick together?
>> That's the question, isn't it? Surely
the Kieran expect us to shoot holes into
each other for their enjoyment. Why else
would they have given us all guns? There
are 11 of us and only one can get their
wish. No point in throwing challenges at
us when we are all each other's
challengers.
>> So, it is a race.
>> If that's what you want to see it as, I
see it more as an inevitable blood bath.
Raise your hands if you are serious
about getting the Kieran's wish so I can
know who I should shoot down early on.
Who do you think my dear dysphoric clown
sibling? Well, there he goes having one
of his gay clown seizures again.
I'm going to start walking. None of you
better pass me now or I'm going to get
agitated.
>> Don't lay him on his back. My hoodies.
He will choke on his own fluids. Lean
him up against a wall. His seizures pass
quicker that way. What are you doing,
Brayburn?
>> Your hoodies have got Arinos, so I got
you.
>> I do not need comforting at this moment.
>> Can I ask what you want to wish for
instead, then?
>> I still haven't decided. Arinos wants me
to help him obtain his wish. Even though
it is something I am unsure if I can
agree with what is it though I wish I
could open up Braburn, you and I are not
at the level of intimacy for me to be
able to comfortably share that
information. If we talked about it,
maybe I could help. Some things are
easier to share with a stranger than
with someone you love.
>> Friendship. Let's go make my wish come
true.
Can I help you, Saurin?
>> Sorry. It's just you have a habit of
betraying us.
>> That we do. What a fun relationship we
have. We should probably hate each
other, but we don't. I won't be doing
anything of the sort unless it's what
Apple Bottom wants.
>> Why are you looking for the Kieran's
wish?
>> I shouldn't say outside of ear distance
from Apple Bottom.
>> I'm right here.
>> Goodness, that you are.
Arinos, do you want to talk about what
you've been going through? You wouldn't
get it, Saurin. Of course I would. You
are literally half me. I'm not you. You.
I'm not half apple bottom and I'm not
ship's puppet either. I'm not saying all
that. It's just that you helped me
before when I was struggling with who I
was after first becoming an Olly Corn.
Clearly, what I'm going through is a
little bit different.
>> So, what are you boys wishing for?
>> Don't talk to Brayburn. Am I not allowed
to make small talk with the sexy [__]
that I'm going to be forced to be with
for the next few hours?
>> No. Keep talking, [__] You're the
only actual Kieran among us. So surely
you must know more about this event than
the rest of us. What's the secret to
getting the Kieran's wish?
>> If I knew that, what makes you think I
would tell you instead of keeping the
information to my
>> Why did you just knock out our entire
travel party?
>> I made a calculated judgment call. They
were giving off deeply untrustworthy
vibes.
Big Mac, Big Mac, get up. Are you okay?
Big Mac took my fall. You saved me. Is
it your life goal to make my life
miserable?
>> I didn't do [__] You just had to give
him that cheeky response when it is
obvious you don't know any more than we
do.
>> What have you been doing to try and cure
his illness? Exactly.
>> Boba tea. Having balls in his mouth
calms him down.
>> You know what I think, Arinos? I don't
think there is a cure for your illness.
In fact, I think friendship may be the
cause of it.
>> He isn't. He's my friend. He wouldn't
make me sick on purpose. Friendship is
not your friend. He's your creator. He
should be able to magically wish any
illness away, I would think.
>> Quit putting disease-ridden thoughts
into his head. He does have a point. He
doesn't. He He doesn't.
>> You two are linked, Arinos knows. If
you're the puppet, that makes friendship
your puppet master.
>> Though the possibility is there, like a
parent passing a recessive gene onto
their child, it would have never been my
intention.
>> I realize something. Surely you've
realized it yourself. Anytime Arenos
glitches out, it's when you are
uncomfortable. Be honest, friendship.
Arenos and I agreed that if either of us
gets the Kieran's wish, we're severing
that tie he has to you so that he can
become a real pony. Will you promise to
make that wish come true for him?
>> I would wish for him to be cured however
it needs to happen. That is as far as I
can say.
>> Even if that means the only way to cure
him is for you to disappear. I'm going
ahead. I won't be like friendship here
and try and dictate your future. Arinos,
you can make the choice yourself whether
or not you trust him near the Kieran's
wish. Catch up when you want to walk
with me. It's exactly as parcel core
says you don't want me to be a real pony
because I won't won't be your puppet any
anymore. No, it's because if you became
a pony, I know you would leave me.
You're more normallooking than I am. You
can pass as a pony. You're already more
charismatic than me. Everyone would
accept you and I would be all alone. Why
should I be forced to keep you company
then? And then and if I'm sick, you know
how much I hate this mind, body,
everything that you gave me. Minutes,
hours at a time. The world just passes
by me. Or does that not even go through
your head?
Become a pony, too, so we can step into
a new world together. I like who I am
even if I'm ugly.
Then continue being ugly inside and out
for your own comfort. Even if it kills
me, I don't want you and I don't need
you. I never needed you.
>> Just go, please.
He may have been the one who created
you, but you've become your own pony
now. He's devolved from your creator to
your parasite, and we need to get him
off of you. My name is a lie. All I am
is a lie. I'm just Saurin's twisted
magic. I was never supposed to make
friends or have emotions of my own. So
why? Why am I trying so hard to be good
for my own puppet, a parasite who
doesn't even love me? What's the point
of loving and caring for others when no
one ever does the same for me in return?
Why did I come here to save you? Why am
I the one trying my best to learn what
friendship is? The only one who's
constantly made to feel bad. So be it
then. If Ponyville doesn't want my
friendship, I swear I won't show any
pony any friendship ever again.
Parcel Core, I've decided on my wish.
>> Oh.
I wish for the both of you to be dead.
>> That's a fun wish.
>> Is that the Kieran's wish?
>> Friendships and parcel cor's wishes are
clashing. So, the Kieran's wish showed
itself to allow itself to be claimed.
How do you know that's what's happening?
>> I don't know. I'm just saying some
[__]
>> Ari knows is in trouble. I can help him
if every pony else can get Parcel core
and friendship to stop fighting.
>> Why stop them from fighting when it
distracts the two of them from my goal?
>> You get back here.
>> What's going on?
>> You're having one of your clown seizures
again.
Your clown seizures are tied to
friendship. Obviously, I know that now.
I hate you, Saurin and Brayburn.
Friendship is just Saurin. And he made
me so that he can have his own Brayburn.
We're not originals. We're just copies
of you.
I'm not even real. If I do not obtain
what I desire most and wish to cut my
strings from friendship, I would be
better off just glitching out of reality
entirely. But you are real.
Just because you're a puppet, it doesn't
mean you have to always be copying
someone else. And you don't need to be a
flesh and blood pony to become the you
that you want to be. But if becoming
real is truly the wish you want to make,
then I'll stand by you, even if
friendship won't. You're right that
friendship is part of me. But he's lived
his own life long enough to become his
own person. Deep down, you know that
too, Ari knows. Friendship is
comfortable with who he is. He doesn't
feel like he needs a new body to be
real. But that doesn't mean he can
decide that for you. But at the same
time, you can't force him to change with
you if he doesn't want it. He's angry
with the world now because you turned
your back on him. And he loves you more
than the whole world. But I think given
enough time, he'll accept whatever
choice you make. trust in each other. I
hit him. I can't take that back.
>> Love isn't made broken by hurting each
other. It's made real by choosing each
other afterward instead of letting the
pain become the end of the story. I felt
his heart break. And do you want that to
be the last thing he feels?
I don't totally hate that friendship and
I are reflections of you two. Because
when I look at what you two have, it
feels like the kind of love that keeps
the whole world turning. It's always
Saurin and Braburn. What was I thinking?
I don't want a life that replaces this
one. I want to repair it because it's
what I love. It's what friendship gave
me.
Hey
Well, you got it. You won. What are you
going to ask for, you little [__]
freak? Fresh bodies and a year'sl long
membership for one of your weird necro
sites.
>> Don't talk like you know me clean sweep.
You only know one side of me.
>> I know far more than one, and they all
make me sick.
>> I was going to wish for your
forgiveness. Okay.
I've never had friends. I take my
frustration out on others the same way
others have taken out their own
frustration on me. I was kicked out of
Kieran Village all because I was gay.
I've lived on the streets and did things
I'm not proud of. And yeah, I may have a
fetish for dead bodies, but who doesn't
at the end of the day? But there's no
point in forgiveness if I'd be forcing
you to do it. So take it.
I want to be better.
>> I can only hope you're serious about
that. There are people out there who
will befriend you after the things
you've done should you really leave it
in the past. But I'm not one of those
people. I will never forgive you.
>> I understand.
>> If you truly want to be better, don't
hurt others the way you hurt me.
It's Professor Kieran. Everybody run.
Halt.
>> You may have kicked me out for being
gay, but this is still my home.
>> Is that what you've been telling others,
you little freak? We kicked you out for
doing you know what in the Kieran
graveyard.
>> I am looking for Prince Kieran. Let me
in to see him.
>> The palace is being renovated, so the
local McDonald's has been turned into a
makeshift throne room. The prince can be
found there. You may see him, but only
for however long he allows.
>> Now, look who I have the honors of
seeing today. The former prince Kieran
himself. Exiled from the village for
digging up dead bodies in the graveyard
to fulfill his unjust desires.
>> I am here to initiate the Kieran's wish
event.
>> You lost the right to seek out the
Kieran's wish since you are no longer
prince. Dirty [__]
>> That's not true. The sacred Kieran texts
state that any Kieran born under
princehood has the right to climb the
steps and seek a wish at least once in
their life. Nowhere does it say that
right can be revoked.
>> Damn. Is your butthole jealous of how
much [__] you just spewed out of your
mouth?
>> Technically, he is not wrong, your
highness. To initiate the event and
participate in it is his birthright as a
once-born royal.
>> Well, [__]
If you're participating, you need to
name nine others.
>> There's a pony called Clean Sweep who
lives in Ponyville. I want him to be a
part of it. The rest don't matter.
>> I'm not going to send my poor innocent
Kirins into an event that will spell
their certain doom just to satisfy your
desire to play these games. Let me call
Princess Celestia, the ruler of
Ponyville, and see if there's any ponies
she wouldn't mind throwing in the trash.
>> What's up? A special event that could
lead to the death of my ponies? Yeah,
I've got a list of like nine gay
stallions I was planning on putting on
death row anyway. I'll send the list
over right away. Why only stallions?
Well, because male ponies in My Little
Pony have the societal rights comparable
to only that of human women. And as
such, it is my job as a government
official to make sure that they stay low
on the food chain. Should they all die,
that will drop the stallion race down
from 48% to like 3%. And I think that
would be funny.
>> I will get my wish, whatever it takes,
and then I can start over and be the
Kieran I want to be.
Uh, I think Zakirin's wish is giving me
one last chance to say goodbye, isn't
it?
>> You're really going home then?
>> You were there for me when nobody else
was Big Mac. Others have only ever found
me annoying, but you came for me in
Stellionrad
and talked me off that ledge. I'll never
forget you as the greatest friend I've
ever had.
Make sure future Saurin treats you like
the best thing he'll ever have because
that is what you are.
You told me how you could let go of
Brain once before and you've gotten
through it after enough time. You let go
of me, too. But you're not braver. What
I had with you, what I want to have with
you is so much more.
Ah, this is really the end of my story,
I suppose.
brighter than
>> the Kieran's wish. My wish
together we'll be all right. Can you see
forever we will go?
>> Ari knows.
>> Ari knows illness isn't your fault.
friendship or because of Arinos himself.
I think it's our fault because you're
the memories of Saurin's darkest day
when he was feeling most alone. You
break down when the friendship you're
giving away isn't equally met. And that
has a physical effect on Arinos. I'm
sorry, friendship. On behalf of
everyone, even though I long for
friendship, I have been reluctant to
open myself up fully to others. So, I am
partially to blame. It would do me some
good to work on that side of myself and
believe ponies when they say they want
to be my friend.
>> Ari knows become the pony you want to
be.
>> I don't think I need it. I think the
both of us became new ponies without it
just now.
I am sorry, but you all must die. The
Kieran prince.
>> The Kieran's wish requires a sacrifice.
You know, after the holder's wish is
said out loud, the hearts of every other
competitor is what's used to make that
wish come true. Nine lives traded for
one single wish.
Shoot me and you shoot him too. You love
this clown, don't you? Why don't you
help me escape? You and he aren't flesh
and blood, which means you will not die
should you allow me to make my wish.
>> Friendship.
You can.
>> What are you doing?
>> I saw these wounds before.
>> I understand. I will trust in my
friends.
The other eight are all dead. It's just
the two of us now. So, which of us is
going to get our wish?
>> Why don't we tell each other our wish
and we can decide who deserves it more.
You go first. From when I was very
young, I've always had something
different about me than others. You
probably noticed what it is by now, but
how I keep my left side covered. I'm not
trying to look cool or anything.
>> Keep talking, Twink. I was born broken
and I wish to make me unbroken.
Because when you're not all put together
in that specific way society wants,
friendship doesn't come easy.
A Kirin is granted only one chance in
their entire life to take part in the
Kieran's wish. And that time I
participated was during a special one.
The former prince Kieran had been cast
out from the Kieran race for stealing
bodies from the graveyard, leaving the
throne empty. So, it was decreed that
whoever won that year's Kieran's wish
would earn more than a single wish. They
would be named the next prince. Because
the Kirins were desperate for a
successor, Kieran lives were valued far
more highly, and the old rule was
loosened. Normally the Kieran's wish
ended only when every other participant
is dead. That wasn't the case when I
played where both the winner and the
runnerup survived. The winner denied the
role as Kieran Royal and walked away
with all he wanted and I got a crown and
a throne which I couldn't care for in
the slightest.
White. No guns or magic.
>> He staff can absorb magical energy.
>> You've hit your fury and it
ignite and turn to embers
like
>> I'm going to help.
Fire. You
spread
>> Big Mac future.
>> Clean sweep. Clearly, we have some
things to talk about once this is all
over.
I wish to have the blood of every living
or non-living creature to have ever
existed, currently exists, or will ever
exist, to flow through my veins. I wish
to become God over my new race of
Oblivion ponies. I wish for the pathway
between Equestria and the world of
wishes to be broken indefinitely. I wish
for the world of wishes to be my domain.
>> That's like nine wishes.
So now what?
>> What is there to do? We're stuck here
forever in this stupid world with a lot
of staircases.
>> Brin, you and Saurin are alicorns. Can't
you just open a portal or some [__]
>> No. Parcel Core specifically wished for
the pathway between our world and the
world of wishes to be broken
indefinitely. Not even magic works.
>> Big Mac, clean sweep. I know you two
have had a long day, but we have some
things to discuss.
>> Yes, we do.
>> My adventure made me realize something.
Uncapable of getting my own wish.
>> My friends, you came. Ari knows. Who are
these [__] My friends from clown
college I told you about. From left to
right, we have Bibble Bop. Cherry
chuckles. Last laugh. andricolor
jubilee. Ah, it is. Nice to meet you
all, I suppose.
>> This sucks. My medication is back home
in my dresser next to my thongs. How am
I going to survive in this new world
unmedicated?
>> Who needs medication when you've got
emotional support from your favorite
Pegasus?
Starting today, I prescribe you a daily
steady dosage of my affection to be
taken generously and preferably while
cuddling with said favorite Pegasus.
I screwed up so royally bad, didn't I?
>> I'm not going to lie to you. Yeah, you
did.
>> I'm going to show you my breathing
technique before my Wonder Bowl
performances. It's not a replacement for
your medication, but maybe it will help
when you're having your skitso episodes.
Breath in. Breath out.
We're stuck here because you interrupted
things. But the alternative would be
nine of us dead and only one getting
their wish. So, is this the absolute
worst thing that could have happened?
Everyone came here chasing that one wish
they thought would make them happy, a
home, a purpose, someone to love, a
chance to become the horse they always
wanted to be. And in the end, they found
it in themselves. Makes me wonder if I
hadn't come to you to start all this,
where would everyone be now?
>> You are just saying things to make me
not feel so bad.
>> Maybe. So, I guess I'm just talking
about myself and hoping they all found
their light, too.
My horn is gone. So are my wings.
>> Brayburn, are you ready to go? I've got
your cowboy candy all packed and ready
to share with every pony.
>> On the outside, I look like a normal
Earth pony again. While on the outside,
everyone in this domain resembles our
base horse types. On the inside were
oblivion ponies. Not much has changed
about all of us except for that we
recently learned we can really survive
off of only water and blood, which is a
good thing since we quickly found out
there wasn't any food to be found here
in the world of wishes. Since Big Mac
and I are the best of the best when it
comes to growing things, we got to work
quickly setting up a farm and we're
teaching Friendships hoodies and Parcel
Cor's shadow ponies how farm work is
done. I guess because parcel core is a
drawing that's technically not alive.
The Kieran's wish granted it for him
without requiring any other living
sacrifices.
I don't know if we should be friendly
with him since he's the one who got us
in this mess. I'm sure our friends and
family are waiting for us back in
Equestria. I know eventually we'll find
our way back to them. But until then,
we're making the best of things. We may
be lost in the world of wishes, but
we're happy together and that's what
matters most. A new arm. Wow. Please do
not give this one away. Making parts for
you cuts into my time. Okay. I want to
thank you, Arios, because I may have
never said this before, but it's always
been on my mind for being my first
friend. First friend? Don't you mean
your only friend? I can't keep calling
you my only friend now that I have more.
If first friend does not sound right to
you, then may I have the permission to
call you my best friend?